(Amy:)You found a loophole?
(Raj:)Sorry I started without you...
(Raj:)...I'm a little nervous.
It's been a long time since I've been on a date.
(Amy:)I can't believe
I bleached my mustache for this.
(Raj:)You should go to my girl,
she'll knock out those sideburns for free.
You know, Amy, I don't think
you and I have had a real conversation.
(Raj:)Let's use tonight
to get to know each other better.
(Raj:)You start.
(Raj:)Go home.
- I don't understand.
- Sheldon, how could you do this?
(Amy:)- It's our second anniversary.
- It's your anniversary?
(Raj:)Oh, my God, I had no idea.
(Raj:)Amy, please, let me make this right.
(Amy:)- Thank you.
- My pleasure. Waiter?
(Raj:)A bottle of champagne
and three glasses.
(Raj:)Oh, boy, isn't this romantic?